[Music]
[Música]
Javi I sleep with you and I wake up
Javi me duermo contigo y me despierto
with you Hey Maria del Carmen don't
contigo oye María del Carmen pues no
say that too loud my wife is going to
digas eso muy fuerte que mi mujer me
kick me out of the house
echa ya de casa
Diego is showing a contract Ah well I'm
Diego está enseñando un contrato Ah pues
going to steal it I'm sorry because it's been
se lo voy a robar lo siento porque lleva
at least four calls without
como mínimo son cuatro convocatorias sin
like this
así
Hey but I say can you show this
Oye pero digo puede mostrar esto
Diego can you show this
Diego puede mostrar esto
you know what he's showing Diego
sabes lo que está enseñando Diego
see man it's that man stealing he's been
lo ves tío es que tío a robar ha estado
an hour and a half an
una hora y media
taking calls from 806 without saying anything I don't
cogiendo llamadas del 806 sin decir nada
know I don't know how much and after an hour and a half he
no sé no sé cuánto y a la hora y media
gives you the exclusive Okay and the exclusive
te da la exclusiva Vale y la exclusiva
is that there's a clause in this contract
es que hay una cláusula de este contrato
that could be Jorge Perez's or it could be
que puede ser de Jorge Pérez o puede ser
a colleague's let's see I have my doubts
de un compañero a ver yo tengo mis dudas
I have my doubts that you can
yo tengo mis dudas de que tú puedas
Show a contract that isn't yours
Mostrar un contrato que no es tuyo
the first thing you how are you going to have a
lo primero que tú cómo vas a tener un
contract
contrato
from a TV personality that isn't
de un personaje de la tele que no seas
you do you
tú
understand
me entendéis
How can you how can you have a copy
Cómo puedes cómo puedes tener una copia
of a contract that isn't in you I think
de un contrato que no estás tú yo creo
that this contract will be from some
que este contrato será de algún
colleague also from unicorn that more or
compañero también de unicornio que más o
less has the same the
menos tenga las mismas
same conditions as him or that
las mismas condiciones que él o que
they predict that they have the same
ellos auguren que tienen las mismas
conditions he
condiciones
knows and the exclusive is
sabe y y la exclusiva es
that they are not going to fire him they are
que no lo van a echar
not going to fire him okay the exclusive is
no lo van a echar vale la exclusiva es
that according to what Jorge
que según lo que está haciendo Jorge
Pérez is doing at the moment he would have done
Pérez en estos momentos habría hecho
some things that could be grounds for
algunas cosas que podrían ser motivo de
dismissal does this mean that they are going to
despido esto quiere decir que lo vayan a
fire him Jorge Pérez no it does not mean
echar al Jorge Pérez no no quiere decir
that they are going to fire him it is his
que lo vayan a echar es el suyo
Ah it is his
Ah es el suyo
But he said that it is his it is his he
Pero ha dicho que sea el suyo
said
lo ha dicho
but if his it
pero si el suyo
is not the same production company no
no es la misma productora no
But he has said that this contract is
Pero él ha dicho que este contrato sea
Jorge's
de Jorge
or has he said that it is his
o ha dicho que es suyo
remove the Javi in ​​case they claim against
quita los Javi no sea que te reclamen a
you They cannot claim anything from me from
ti A mí no me pueden reclamar nada de
another thing that other people have published
otra de otra cosa que hayan publicado
or in other words
o sea
the exclusive would be a contract
la exclusiva sería un contrato
that could have the same clauses as
que podría tener la misma cláusulas que
a contract of Jorge I have to
un contrato de Jorge
see this I will be calm
esto lo tengo que ver Yo tranquilo
tomorrow
mañana
or in other words he has affirmed that this is Jorge's
o sea él ha afirmado que esto es de
And how can he have a contract that is not
Y cómo puede tener el un contrato que no
his
es suyo
and publish it
y publicarlo
or in other words publish a page he
o sea publicar una página
has taken out the contract and has not said
ha sacado el contrato y no ha dicho de
who it is
quién es
or in other words he has taken out the contract and has not
o sea ha sacado el contrato y no ha
said who it is
dicho de quién es
yes but the title of the live broadcast is
si ya pero el título del directo es
exclusive Jorge Pérez on the street
exclusiva Jorge Pérez a la calle
said that it was Jorge's  the little time that I've
decía que era de Jorge el poco rato que
seen it Well, it's that I do
lo he visto
n't understand how you can
Pues es que no entiendo cómo puedes
show a document
mostrar un documento
that isn't yours. I think the
que no es tuyo yo lo que creo que la
trick here will be that the contract
trampa aquí estará en que el contrato no
isn't Jorge's Wait, I'm
es de Jorge Espérate que estoy
listening, the lukewarm one
escuchando el tibio
wants to come here,
quiere venir aquí
want to come here?
quieres venir aquí
No then, almost this way
no entonces casi por aquí
[Music] I do
[Música]
n't know, the truth, I think this is, let's see, I think this is
no sé la verdad yo creo que esto a ver
n't Jorge's, I think
yo creo que esto no es de Jorge
this isn't Jorge's, I think
yo creo que esto no es de Jorge yo creo
this is his contract, it does
que esto es un contrato
n't make sense that you start
es que no tiene sentido que te pongas a
showing a contract that isn't yours,
mostrar un contrato que no sea el tuyo
the pull goes from this Setup, yeah, yeah, but I
el tirón pasa de este Setup ya ya pero
think I was listening to it over there, he
creo que lo estaba escuchando por ahí él
doesn't usually, he doesn't go into the
no suele él no entra para dentro de las
rooms or the hallway, no, he doesn't usually go
habitaciones y del pasillo no no suele
in. I don't know if something happened to him No, but I
entrar no sé si le pasaba algo No pero
called him now, he doesn't give a damn about me,
lo he llamado ya suda un poco de mí
legally, he can only show his
legalmente puede mostrar solo su
contract, even if he has a
contrato aunque tenga el contrato
confidential contract from someone else, he can't show it,
confidencial de otro no lo puede mostrar
obviously, as a journalist.
claro evidentemente como periodista
Well, he's not a journalist, Diego, he's a
Bueno no es periodista Diego es
paparazzi, it
paparazzi no
can't be a prototype, it could be a thousand
puede ser un prototipo pueden ser mil
things, we'll never know the
cosas nunca lo sabremos la cláusula de
termination clause expressed, let's see. These are
resolución expresada a ver Estos son
so that you understand, the page that is being
para que me entendáis la página que está
shown are the parts of the  contract
enseñando son las partes del contrato
that they are indicating to you
que te están indicando
cases in which the company could
casos en los que la empresa podría
fire you
echarte
without fulfilling the contract okay And then they
sin cumplir el contrato vale Y entonces
have to give it seems like the
tienen que dar parecen las cláusulas
standard clauses of the Mediaset contracts if they don't
tipo de los contratos de mediaset si no
put the signatories person shrugging
ponen los firmantes persona encogida de
shoulders
hombres
Emilio can you look at me if It is legal for you to
Emilio puedes mirarme si Es legal que tú
show a contract that is not yours It's that I
muestres un contrato que no sea tuyo
have it's that I think that not eh Let's
Es que tengo es que yo creo que no eh A
see I'm not a lawyer but it doesn't sound to me that you
ver no soy abogado pero no me suena que
can do that It
eso lo puedas hacer
doesn't sound to me that you can do that let's
no me suena que eso lo puedas hacer a
see These are the clauses not of the entire
ver Estos son las cláusulas no de todo
contract
el contrato
These are the clauses
Estos son las cláusulas
that indicate why the company
que indican por qué motivo la empresa
could take and fire you with one hand
podría [__] y despedirte con una mano
behind and the other in front and they are usually for
atrás y otra delante y suelen ser por
several clauses not that leaving the
varias cláusulas no que abandone el
set without reason that
plató sin motivo que
missing work without
que falta el trabajo sin sin
authorization or without justification for I do
autorización o sin justificación durante
n't know how many weeks that
no sé cuántas semanas
coming dressed in underwear and
que venga vestido en calzones y en
suspenders okay I remember that Antonio
tirantas vale me acuerdo que Antonio
David who appeared in the in one of the
David que salió en la en una de la
sentence had a clause that said that it
sentencia tenía una cláusula que decía
could be grounds for dismissal That he did not
que podría ser motivo de despido Que no
follow the guidelines of the program that
siguiera con las pautas del programa que
that can be interpreted in many
eso se puede interpretar de muchas
ways okay go ahead and
maneras vale
show your license plate it doesn't
va enseñando matrícula tampoco me
surprise me either Well yes In that sense Yes
sorprende Bueno sí En ese sentido Sí
but the license plates don't  It's what I was
pero las matrículas no es lo estuve
watching and when I got the license plate I had
viendo y había que cuando la matrícula
to file a complaint in case
había que poner denuncia por si pasaba
something happened to my data because of the
algo con mis datos por culpa de lo de la
license plate but as such showing it wasn't
matrícula pero como tal mostrarla no era
knowing
saber
but the production company is different I think
pero la productora son diferente yo creo
that I think it's not Jorge's contract
que yo creo que no es un contrato de
okay we will never know we will never
Jorge vale nunca lo sabremos nunca lo
know but I think it won't be
sabremos pero yo creo que no será un
Jorge's contract I think it will be an
contrato de Jorge yo creo que será un
example contract and that's it Okay and what
contrato de ejemplo y ya está Vale y lo
Jorge is telling you I mean the
que te está diciendo Jorge O sea la
exclusive it's not that they're throwing Jorge out on the street I do
exclusiva no es que echen a la calle
n't know if you're getting the clip
no sé si estáis pillando el clip Me
the click seems very Hardcore to me
parece muy Hardcore el click
the clip seems very Hardcore I
Me parece muy Hardcore el clip
mean the clickbait have you understood it have you
o sea el clickbait lo habéis entendido
understood the clickbai is the
lo habéis entendido el clickbai es el
clickbait is that in that contract that
clickbait es que en ese contrato que te
Diego is showing you that could be that
está enseñando Diego que podría ser el
of some Telecinco collaborator Like
de algún colaborador de telecinco Como
for example Jorge Pérez
por ejemplo Jorge Pérez
in those clauses they
en esa cláusulas
indicate that what
te indican que lo que está haciendo
Jorge is doing at the moment
Jorge en estos momentos
could be grounds for dismissal
podría ser motivo de despido
What is Jorge doing at the
Qué es lo que está haciendo Jorge en
moment well, missing
estos momentos pues faltar faltar al
work for a lot of days and he
trabajo durante un montón de días y ni
's not even picking up the phone to
siquiera le está cogiendo el teléfono a
the production company to give him any kind of
la productora para darle ningún tipo de
explanation I
explicación
mean
O sea
the  The exclusive that
la exclusiva que está que está dando
Diego Arrabal is giving is not that he's been
Diego arrabal no es que lo hayan
fired.
despedido
The exclusive that Diego Arrabal is giving
la exclusiva que está dando Diego
after two hours
después de dos horas
is that he could be fired.
es que lo podrían echar
[Music]
[Música]